OMONIYI OLUWASEUN STEPHEN



Contact

Address:

34, Kuffo Street, Ayobo, Lagos, Nigeria.

Phone:

+234 8105055868

Email:

omoniyioluwaseun22@gmail.com

Language:

English

Projects

- ABI: African Blockchain Institute (https://africablockchain.institute.com
- Beta News: A news web app (https://betanews.herokuapp.com)
- Technicon: A web app for easy delivery and monitoring of repair services. (https://www.technicon.ng)
- (<u>nttps://www.technicon.ng</u>)Resumé: My Resume

(https://gifted-austin-

 645f13.netlify.app)
IPF: Indian Professional Forum (https://www.ipfnigeria.ng)

Summary

Senior Full Stack Developer specializing in Web and Mobile development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic Web and Mobile projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages and frameworks including HTML5, TypeScript, Testing (Jest & Enzymes), JavaScript, CSS 3, MD-Bootstrap 4, React JS, Webpack, Graph QL, React Native, OOP, Material UI, MySQL, Mongo DB, Python, AWS.

Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Front End Designing
- Complex problem solver (Algorithm)
- Mobile Development
- Creative design
- REST API designing
- DataBase Management
- Web Development
- Cloud Computing (AWS)

Education

BSc. Pure and Applied Economics - 2018 to 2022

Experience

Front End Developer- 09/2017 to 12/2018

Build Code Together, Lagos, Nigeria

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.

Full Stack Developer- 01/2019 to 10/2020 Benny Tech, Lagos, Nigeria

- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.